用人来比啊，我说像…
In human terms? I'd say...
…西碧雪佛（著名电视明星）
... Cybill Shepherd.
你们是在电影里演出 还是你们有妄想症？
So you guys in the movie or you just really paranoid?
沙尔？
Hey,Sal?
杰利想知道 猴子可以上地铁那一幕了吗？
Jerry wants to know if the monkey's ready.
抱歉
Excuse me?
杰利是导演吗？他是哪一个？
Jerry is the director? Which one's he?
就是坐在导演椅子那个 我懂了
-The one in the director's chair? -Gotcha.
菲比，我们走
Pheebs,walk with me.
我干嘛要跟你走？
Why am I walking with you?
我们只是要走过来这里 远离那些…
We're just going over here so that we can get away from...
…嗜血肉的可怕病毒
...the horrible flesh-eating virus!
看在老天的份上，听我说
For the love of God,woman,listen to me!
他有没有在看？有没有在看？
Is he looking? Is he looking?
（茱莉亚罗伯茨）我有个难题 告诉我啊
-We've got a problem. -Tell me.
我没有办法帮克丽化妆
I can't do Chris' makeup.
她拒绝承认她的嘴巴上有胡子
She refuses to acknowledge her mustache.
很多吗？ 像眉毛掉到嘴上似的
-ls it bad? -lt looks like her eyebrow fell down.
除非有人说服她 让我帮她漂白…
Unless we convince her to let me bleach it...
…不然尚格云顿（动作明星）就得去跟加比卡普兰（男星）亲热了
...Van Damme will be making out with Gabe Kaplan.
我去跟她谈谈
I'll talk to her.
我讨厌演员
I hate actors.
老兄，伪装得不错 我刚才差点没看到你
Nice camouflage. For a minute there,I almost didn't see you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
你叫钱德吗？
Is your name Chandler?
对，没错
Yes,it is.
钱德宾
Chandler Bing.
你认识我？ 还是你很会钓男人？
Do you know me or are you just really good at this game?
我是苏西莫斯
I'm Susie Moss.
四年级呀，戴眼镜
Fourth grade? Glasses?
我常常像拿手提包一样 拿一包动物饼干
I carried a box of animal crackers like a purse?
苏西莫斯
Susie Moss!
对呀，是呀
Right! Yeah! Wow!
你真是…
You look....
发育得太棒了
Great job growing up.
很高兴看到你不再戴那顶 缀满小镜子的牛仔帽
It's nice to see you don't still wear the cap with the mirrors on it.
升上五年级之后 我发现我不是个男妓
I graduated fourth grade and realized I wasn't a pimp.
记得班上的话剧吗？
Remember the class play?
你掀我的裙子 全礼堂的人都看到我的内裤了
You pulled up my skirt and the entire auditorium saw my underpants?
对，那个时候 我用我的幽默感来保护自己
Yes. Back then,I used humor as a defense mechanism.
谢天谢地，我现在不用那样了
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
那么，儿童时代以来你一直在干什么呢？
So? What have you been doing since childhood?
哦，我有了条新的腰带
Well, I got a new belt.
我很好奇
I wondered
天啊… 怎么了？
-Oh,my God! -What? What?
是尚格云顿
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
我不知道他在这部电影里面 他好帅啊
I didn't know he was in this movie. He is so hot!
真的吗？
You think?
绰号“来自布鲁塞尔的肌肉 -悍将尚格云顿
The Muscles from Brussels? Wham-Bam-Van-Damme?
你看过“时空特警”吗？
Did you see Time Cop?
没有啊，他演得很好吗？
No. Was he any good in it?
瑞秋，他完全改变了时空
Rachel,he totally changed time!
那你过去跟他讲话嘛
So why don't you go talk to him?
你过去告诉他，他很可爱 最糟能怎样呢？
Go tell him he's cute. What's the worst that could happen?
他会听到的
He could hear me.
好吧，我去帮你讲 瑞秋，不要…
-I'm doing it for you. -Don't you dare! Don't!
不要
Don't!
告诉他我会做菜
Tell him I cook!
对不起
Excuse me.
这样会有一点怪怪的…
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
…我那边那个朋友…
... but my friend over there...
…她很会做菜…
...who cooks,by the way....
她觉得你很可爱
She thinks you're cute.
你不这么觉得吗？
You don't think I'm cute?
我不知道
I don't know.
你觉得你可爱吗？
Do you think you're cute?
我们扯太远了 我是过来告诉你…
We're getting off the track. I was supposed to tell you...
…我朋友她觉得你很可爱
... my friend thinks you're cute.
我该怎么告诉她呢？
What should I tell her?
告诉她 我觉得她的朋友，很可爱
You can tell her I think her friend is cute.
斯蒂芬赫斯为了钱而吃东西
Stephen Hurs would eat things for money.
大卫斯坦没有手了
David Stein had no elbows.
就是那个被发现手淫的家伙？
Who got caught masturbating?
那不是他干的，他当时只是为了乘公交车的钱
That's not what he was doing.He was looking for his bus money.
化妆  叫我了，我得走了
-Makeup! -That's me. I gotta go.
我得碰你老兄的手多少次 你才会开尊口约我出去呢？
How many times must I touch you on the arm before you ask me on a date?
我想再试一次
Well,let's try one more.
我们去“厄尼”，八点钟
There you go. Ernie's,8:00?
我会到
I'll be there.
谁知道，一切顺利的话 或许这一次…
And if things go well,maybe this time...
…我能看到你的内裤
... I'll get to see your underwear.
居然没人听到这句话？
No one was around to hear that?
他怎么说？
So what'd he say?
他真浑蛋
What a jerk!
我一直在跟他谈你 可是他却一直想要约我
I kept talking about you,and he kept asking me out.
我当然是说不行
Naturally,you know,I said no.
还是谢了
Thanks,anyway.
但是他一直约我…
He just kept asking...
…约我…
...and asking,asking,asking....
如果你想跟他约会的话就去啊
If you want to go out with him,you can.
他听起来像是个浑蛋，但…
Sounds like a jerk to me,but
尚格云顿，她说好，今晚见
Jean-Claude,she said yes! I'll see you tonight!
谢谢
Thank you.
然后 尚格云顿带我去“十字路口”…
Then Jean-Claude took me to Crossroads...
…我们在那里 跟茱儿芭莉摩（女星）鬼混
...and we hung out with Drew Barrymore.
老兄，她好惹火
Oh,man. She's so smokin'!
她有一对最炫的…
She's got the greatest set of
这儿没男的？
No guys around,huh?
有谁需要什么吗？ 我来杯浓缩咖啡
-Does anybody need anything? -I'll have an espresso.
我还是自己去拿
I'll get it.
叫你去的话 说不定最后会被你喝掉
If I ask you to,you'll end up drinking it yourself.
好不公平啊 我知道
-That is so unfair. -I know.
你跟尚格云顿那样对她之后 还要喝她的咖啡吗？
Like you'd drink her coffee after what you did to her with Van Damme?
乔伊，我要取消今晚的壁球
I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
马修的训练师会把马修让给我几个小时
Marcel's trainer will let me have him for a couple of hours.
你为了猴子失我的约？
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
我们可以改星期六打呀
We can reschedule for Saturday.
对，除非你搭上一票鸽子
Unless you hook up with a bunch of pigeons.
用叉子叉我…
Stick a fork in me...
…我熟了
... I am done!
用叉子什么？
Stick a fork what?
像你煎牛排那样啊
Like when you're cooking a steak.
我不吃肉的
I don't eat meat.
那你怎么知道菜熟了呢？
How do you know vegetables are done?
不知道啊 只要吃一口就知道了
Well,you don't. You eat them and you can tell.
那吃我吧，我熟了
Okay,then eat me,I'm done!
我遇见完美的女人了
I've met the perfect woman.
我们坐在沙发上 我们在亲热…
We're sitting on her couch,fooling around...
…突然她转过来对我说：
...and then she turns to me and says:
“你有想过在电梯里做吗？”
"Did you ever want to do it in an elevator?"
那你说什么？
What did you say?
我相信我的回答是…
I believe my exact words were....
你怎么知道 要不要在电梯里做？
How do you know if you wanna do that?
你就是知道
You just know.
我们得走了 三十分钟后订了餐厅位置
We gotta go. Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
我的计划最多绝对不会 超过两，三分钟的
What I had planned shouldn't take more than two,three minutes,tops.
两百秒钟的激情，我们得走了
Two hundred seconds of passion! We gotta go.
但是…
But...
…我有个主意
... here's an idea.
你有没有穿过女人的内衣呀？
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
这个事实上，有…
Well,yes,actually...
…是我艾达姑妈的
... but they were my Aunt Edna's.
一条裤子里挤了三个人
And there were three of us in there.
我在想，如果你今天…
I was thinking it would be kind of sexy...
…晚饭的时候穿我的内衣 会蛮性感的
...if you wore mine tonight at dinner.
你要我穿你内裤？
You want me to wear your panties?
可以吗？
Could you?
若我穿了你内裤的话，那么…
If I was wearing your underwear...
…你要穿什么？
...then what would you be wearing?
你太棒了
You're swell!
音乐准备好了，饭菜也好了
Got the music. Got the dinner.
我做了马修最喜欢吃的菜 香蕉蛋糕…
I made Marcel's favorite dish,banana cake...
…加了虫虫
...with mealworm.
蜡烛啊
Candle.
你以为今天晚上 这儿会发生什么事啊？
What do you think's gonna happen here tonight?
你正要过来…
Hi,are you on your way over
不会…我理解 我是说，猴子得工作嘛
No,I understand. A monkey's gotta work.
不，没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
又不是说… 我计划了什么特别的
It's not like I had anything special planned.
是的，没问题
Yeah. Okay.
好的，再见
Okay. Bye.
真遗憾
I'm sorry, man.
-觉得怎么样 -什么？
-Feel that? -What?
我们是不是应该松开手了
The moment we should have stopped holding hands?.
瑞秋 那我们就由你先开始说好了
Rachel,why don't you start talking first?
好吧，我觉得 她这样是完全没道理的
I feel that this is totally unjustified.
她说我可以的 我又没做什么…
She gave me the green light,I did nothing
你以为 我在电视上看不到你吗？
Do you think I can't see you in the TV set?
好了，莫妮卡 你有什么话要说就说好了…
If there's something you'd like to share
你没有这个权利跟他出去
You had no right to date him!
你这么说太荒唐了吧 你出卖我
-That's the most ridiculous -You sold me out!
我才没有出卖你呢 有，你有
-I did not! -You absolutely
你让我讲好不好？
Would you let me talk!
你刚刚弹我的头？
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完，我只是想…
Well,you wouldn't let me finish and I was
好痛啊
That hurt!
别弹了
Quit flicking!
你，你别弹了
Stop flicking!
是你先弹的，是你先弹的
You flicked me first!
别这样，别这样嘛
Let's not do this!
想点快乐的事！
Happy thoughts!
好吧，我要教训人了
Now I'm gonna kick some ass!
好吧 你们住手的话我就放手
All right. Now,I will let go if you both stop.
你要我不再见他吗？
You want me to stop seeing him?
你要我打电话给他 告诉他你要替我跟他约会吗？
You want me to just tell him you're seeing him instead?
你想这样吗？
Is that what you want?
你就是想这样？ 是的
That's what you want?
很好 很好
-Fine! -Fine!
好了
There we go.
我们要是在监狱里的话 你们就会是我的贱女人
If we were in prison,you guys would be,like,my bitches.
谢谢你们让我跟你们一起
Thanks for letting me tag along.
没什么
Forget about it.
你觉得怎么样，扭动先生？
How you doing there,squirmy?
我窝在里面
I'm hanging in.
有一点出来
And a little out.
你是导演的助理？
So assistant to the director?
你的工作一定很有意思 你一定有很多很酷的责任…
That's an exciting job. You must have a ton of responsibilities
我跟选角完全无关
I don't do the casting.
你们大家想吃什么？
So what are you guys gonna eat?
为什么我满脑子 都想着把那冰块放进嘴里…
How come all I can think about is putting that ice in my mouth...
…然后舔遍你的全身？
...and licking you all over?
因为我上的高中是男校 现在神要补偿我？
Because I went to an all-boys high school,and God is making up for it?
我现在就要你…
I want you right here...
…在这里
... right now.
现在？在这里？
Right now,right here?
你不认为这里是公共场所吗？
Don't you think we're in kind of a public place?
这里有活虾
They do have the shrimp.
到洗手间等我
Meet me in the bathroom.
现在我要去洗手间了
I'm going to the bathroom now.
他喜欢把我们留在圈里面
He likes to keep us in the loop.
来呀
Come on.
不敢相信我们在做这事
I can't believe we're doing this.
好，先生
All right,mister.
给我看那条内裤
Let's see those panties.
遵命
Alrighty.
你知道怎么样会更性感吗？
But you know what would be even sexier?
怎么样？
What?
你没把你的衬衫塞进去的话
If you didn't have your shirt tucked into them.
好，现在呢 我想看你只穿那件内裤
All right. Now,I would like to see you wearing nothing but them.
把衣服脱下来
Take your clothes off.
好吧，但是你要知道这表示 我们会错过特餐的介绍
I hope you realize this means we'll miss hearing about the specials.
来，快点…
Come on,hurry!
你要我快点弄好 还是要我做得好？
Do you want this done quick or done right?
好，转过去，我要看你的后面
All right,turn around. I wanna see you from behind.
有人跟着 “钢铁玻璃”录影带做运动哦
Somebody's been doing his Buns of Steel video.
所以你要我缩紧什么吗？ 或者是…
So you want me to clench anything or...?
苏西…
Susie?
这个就是报四年级的仇
This is for the fourth grade.
什么意思啊？ 什么“什么意思”？
-What do you mean? -What do I mean?
什么意思？！
What do I mean?!
我的意思是内裤，先生 那就是我的意思
I mean underpants,mister! That's what I mean!
什么意思？
What? What do you mean?
我的裙子…
My skirt...
…你掀开了，大家笑了
...you lifted. IKids laughing!
到十八岁大家还叫我内裤苏西
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18!
那是四年级的事了 你怎会到现在都还在生气呢？
That was in fourth grade! How could you still be upset?
你二十年后打电话给我 告诉我你是不是还在生气
Call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset about this.
我也要告诉你 你这条内裤我是不会还你的
I hope you realize you're not getting these underpants back!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
两个礼拜前 我还在看“绝命杀阵”…
Just two weeks ago,I was watching Sudden Death...
…现在我竟然在跟尚格云顿约会
...and now I'm on a date with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
你能打扁那个家伙吗？
Can you beat up that guy?
扁这个呢？当然
-Can you beat up that guy? -Sure.
这太疯狂了
This is so wild.
我得承认我有点奇怪 你会同意跟我来个盲目约会
I gotta admit,I was surprised that you agreed to go on a blind date.
通常我是不会答应的
Normally,I would not do it.
是吗？ 那你为什么会为我破例呢？
What made you make the exception for me?
因为瑞秋告诉我说…
Rachel told me...
…你想跟我还有茱儿芭莉摩 来个“三人行”啊
...you were dying to have a threesome with me and Drew Barrymore.
对了，茱儿她有一些规矩的…
By the way,Drew has some ground rules and....
-说你对不起我 -不
-Say you're sorry -No
说！
Say it!
不，我才不要跟你说抱歉呢
No! I'm not gonna!
快说…好极了
Say it! Say it! Great!
瑞秋，道歉 不然你的毛衣就遭殃
Say you're sorry or your sweater gets it.
那是我最喜欢的毛衣 我第三次约会的毛衣
That is my favorite sweater! That is my third-date sweater!
说，你很抱歉
Say you're sorry.
你想玩，是不是？
You wanna play? Okay,let's play.
好，咱们就来玩
Let's play.
你想怎么样？
What'll you do?
把毛衣还给我 否则这就变成番茄酱皮包了
Give me back my sweater or it's handbag marinara.
你才不敢这么做
You don't have the guts.
是吗？至少我不会不敢 告诉男人，我觉得他很可爱
Yeah? At least I wasn't too chicken to tell some guy he was cute.
好了，住手，疯婆子
Stop! Stop the madness!
你们两个疯了
This is crazy!
现在你们谁还记得 你们本来在吵些什么东西吗？
Who can remember why you're fighting in the first place?
对，没错
Yes,that's right.
但是…
But still....
看看你的皮包
Look at your purse!
看看你的毛衣
Look at your sweater!
看看你们自己
Look at yourselves!
我会帮你补毛衣的
I'll help you fix your sweater.
我会帮你…
I'll help you...
…丢掉皮包
...throw out your purse.
对不起，我阻止你再见他
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
对不起 我知道你喜欢他还跟他约会
I'm sorry I went out with him when I knew you liked him.
对不起，我…借了你的手套
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
乔伊？
Joey?
妈？
Ma?
钱德？你在这儿干嘛？ 我以为你们走了
Chandler？What are you doing here? I thought you guys took off.
不不不，是她走了，带着我的衣服
She took off with my clothes!
你一丝不挂 不完全是
-Are you naked in there? -Well,not exactly.
我穿着女生内裤
I'm wearing panties.
你经常穿女生内裤吗？
You always wear panties?
不…这是第一次
No,no. This is the first time.
你还真够倒霉
Talk about your bad luck!
第一次试女生内裤 然后衣服就被别人给带走了
The first time you try panties and someone walks off with your clothes.
不是我要穿的 是苏西叫我穿的
I was not trying them out. Susie asked me to wear them.
让我看看 不要
Let me see!
我才不让你或任何人看呢
No! I'm not letting you or anybody else see,ever!
好吧…
All right,all right!
有人在用“牙线”
Someone's flossing!
乔伊，有些人不喜欢那样的
Joey,some people don't like that.
钱德穿女生内裤
Chandler's wearing panties.
什么？
What?
让我看 不…你不要看
-Let me see! -You don't have to see!
小屁屁
Hi,tushy!
你们谁把你们的内裤借我穿
One of you give me your underpants.
帮不上忙，我不穿内裤的
I'm not wearing any.
你怎么会没穿内裤呢？
How can you not be wearing any?
穿粉红丁字裤的人 倒训起人来了
I'm getting heat from the guy in the hot pink thong.
听我说，罗斯，我出五十块钱 买你的内裤，好吗？
Look,Ross. I'll give you $50 for your underpants.
中央公园
菲比，牛奶用完给我好吗？ 我快好了
-Can I have the milk? -I'm almost done with it.
拉住裤裤不要急嘛
Keep your panties on.
各位，我在电影里了
And I'm in the movie!
怎么了？ 有个扮演病人的请病假…
-What happened? -A virus victim called in sick...
…所以凯西就推荐我上场 我会死在担架上
...so Cathy recommended me and boom! I'm dying on a gurney!
罗斯，马修刚拍完最后一幕 如果你要去现场跟他道别就…
Marcel just finished his last scene,if you wanna go say goodbye.
不，没关系啦 他说不定还有派对什么的要去
That's okay. He's probably got parties to go to and stuff.
他继续他的生活了 生活就是这样子，对不对？
He's moved on. That's the way it goes,right?
天啊
Oh,my God!
什么？
What?
看来我们成功了
Looks like we made it
成功忘记对方…
Left each other on the way...
…找到新欢
... to another love
看来我们成功了
Looks like we made it
今天以前，我还如是想
Or I thought so,till today
直到看到你为止
Until you were there,everywhere
看到你，往日回忆涌上心头
And all I could taste was Love the way we made it
看来我们成功了
Looks like we made it
很遗憾我们之间没有结果，我们也是
Sorry it didn't work out between us.Or us.
茱儿很失望
Drew was very disappointed.
好的，再见
Okay. Well, bye.
再见
Goodbye.
我也说再见
Well, bye for me too.
好，再次再见
Okay. Well, bye-bye again.
好的
Okay.
或许咱们三个人可以…
Perhaps the three of us just could:
哦不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
确定吗？我的屁股可以挤碎核桃哦
Are you sure?.I can crush a walnut with my butt.
-不不不，很难忘 -但是不了
-Oh, no, no, no. Impressive -But no.
也许我在煮饭的时候可以用得上
Maybe if I were baking.
好了，再见
Okay. Bye-bye.
再见，马修
Bye, Marcel.
银幕上见了
See you on the big screen.
是你让人们喝那种啤酒的对吧
You keep people drinking that beer, okay?.
我会想你的，兄弟
I'll miss you, buddy.
再见
Bye.
我想我应该写一首 关于这件事的歌
I think I want to write a song about all this.
只是我的吉他有条弦断了
Except one of the strings on my guitar is broken.
钱德，丁字裤借我，好吗？
Chandler,can I borrow your G-string?
你等说这句话等了很久了吧？ 大概二十分钟啊
-How long you been waiting to say that? -About 20 minutes!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
停
Cut!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人快死了
Can't you see what's going on here? This man is dying!
妈咪
Mommy!
你们看不出来吗？ 这个人已经死了
Can't you see what's going on? This man is dead!